(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
The night shines brighter when she sings...
Special guests are here to join the fun so don't blink
The moment we've all been waiting for...
Ha-ah... uh-uh-uh-ah...
こんなことになんなんて
That things would end up like this...
会う前には分かってたら
If only I'd known before we met,
もう少しだけしゃんとした僕を
then maybe I could have shown you...
見せられたはずなんだ
a slightly more composed version of myself.
「どうしたらいいのかな」なんて
"What should I do?"
頭では分かってるけど
I know the answer in my head, but...
何気ないちょっとした言葉で
With just a few casual words...
Wow oh
嬉し顔が出ちゃって
A happy look escapes my face.
こんなバレバレじゃ格好悪いな
It's embarrassing how obvious I am.
けどこのままじゃ引き下がれないよな
But I can't just back down like this.
今も顔が照れくさくて
Even now, my face is turning red...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I can't say that I'm in love with you.
この気持ち伝わるから
Since these feelings will reach you,
嫌いだってキャラ回り
I act like I hate you instead,
何も言えず またさよなら
and with nothing said, it's goodbye again.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much I can't stand it.
明日こそは言えるかな
I wonder if I can say it tomorrow.
あなたも僕に同じように
I wonder if you're also
恋してたらなんて考えちゃうんだ
in love with me, the same way...
会えない日が続いてる
The days we can't meet keep going on.
このままじゃよろしくない
It's not good to leave things like this.
会ったところで何ができるって
It's not like I can do much
わけじゃないんだけど
even if we did meet, but...
こんな恋は二度とないな
A love like this will never happen again.
頭では分かってるけど
I know that in my head, but...
眩しすぎるその笑顔が
That smile of yours is so dazzling...
Wow oh
僕を焦らせるんだ
It makes me so restless.
ずっと見ていたくなるような
The kind I want to keep looking at forever,
目そらしたくなってしまうよな
but also makes me want to look away.
こんな気持ち分かるのかな
I wonder if you'd understand this feeling.
あなたが笑ってるなら それでいいんです
As long as you're laughing, that's enough.
でも隣は僕がいいな
But I wish I was the one by your side.
もしかしたら実は ずっと
Maybe, actually, all this time...
気付いてるんじゃないかな
you've already noticed, haven't you?
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much I can't stand it.
明日こそは
Tomorrow, for sure...
言えるかな
I wonder if I can say it
全てをひっくり返すくらいの
To the point of turning everything upside down,
粋なセリフは言えそうにないや
I don't think I can say any stylish lines
どうしたってこの気持ちは
No matter what, these feelings...
抑えられそうにはないんだ
...don't seem like they can be suppressed
あなたと出会ったあの日から
Since the day I met you,
ずっと気持ちは変わらない けど
my feelings haven't changed, but...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I can't say that I love you
この気持ち伝わるかな
I wonder if these feelings will reach you
足踏みだって空回り
My steps are just running in place,
何も言えずまたさよなら
unable to say anything, goodbye again
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much I can't stand it
明日こそは言いたいな
I want to say it tomorrow for sure
あなたも僕と同じように
If you were in love just like me,
恋してたらなんて考えてる
I'm thinking about it...
でも分かってる
But I know...
考えすぎってこと
...that I'm overthinking it
Kobo-Kobo-Kobo-Kanaeru at your service!
Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Hehe!
Hi everyone! こぼんわ！ こぼ・かなえるです！
Hi everyone! Kobon-wa! I'm Kobo Kanaeru!
こぼの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru's 3D Birthday Stream 2025!
How was Kobo's performance? Hmm? Hmm?
どうだった？
How was it?
またギターで出てきたよね。へへ。
I came out with a guitar again, didn't I? Hehe.
ちょっと待って... Let me put the guitar down first.
Wait a second... Let me put the guitar down first.
よしよしよしよし... おんしょ...
There we go... and heave-ho...
Okay. Fuu... Hai!
Okay. Phew... Alright!
Once again, welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream 2025!
こぼの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream!
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an...
アイドルみたいコンサート themed 3D birthday stream...
...idol-like concert themed 3D birthday stream...
...for about an hour with many awesome guests!
I bet you guys can't wait! Ni-ni-ni-ni-ni!
I bet you guys can't wait! *Giggles*
Eh? Kobo, why is your stage different?
Ah, chat, nice eyes, chat! You noticed it!
Yeah, you're right! Look at Kobo's new stage!
Wah! でかい！ 新しいステージだよ！
Wah! It's huge! It's a new stage!
There's a big Cilus right here. Big Cilus.
うにょうにょ うにょうにょ...
Squish squish, squish squish...
Hehe! And so many stars! Stars! So many stars!
And then, a big, a big rainbow right here!
And so many clouds because... I don't know,
I think it's just very aesthetic. Yeah!
And the floor! Floor みて！ わー！
And the floor! Look at the floor! Wah!
なんかパターン... 海みたい。
It's like a pattern... like the sea.
You know? Yeah, like my hair! Hehe!
So... um, don't forget to take a lot of screenshots,
especially later, okay? Get a lot of screenshots!
And then post your comments, your moments,
your impressions with hashtag #3DKobornDay2025.
そして Kobo の 3D バースデー配信、SNS にハッシュタグ
And for Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream, on SNS, with the hashtag
#3DKobornDay2025 をつけて
#3DKobornDay2025,
コメントや思い出、感想などなど投稿してね！
please post your comments, memories, and impressions!
And... right. Are you guys ready for the next performance?
Ready ready ready? Okay, let's go to the next performance!
Hmm... wait, I try to remember...
My last position... next position...
あ、OK！歌います。
Ah, okay! I'll sing.
それでは皆さん、準備いいか？
So then everyone, are you ready?
Let's go to the next song!
とくべチュ、して
Give me a special kiss
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, 'I love you' isn't enough
一番 大事がい
Being the most important is best
君がつくるオリジナルの
The original one that you create
特別チュして
Give me a special kiss
眩しくて 目が覚めて
It's so bright that I wake up
愛おしく思ってよ
Please think of me fondly
眠り姫のように
Like a sleeping princess
優しく口づけて
Gently kiss me
夢見た この世界
This world I dreamed of
夕暮れ時 君がいる
At twilight, you are here
全てに触れずに
Without touching everything
二人だけでいよう
Let's be just the two of us
私のこと 独占して
Monopolize me
君だけのものになってもいい
It's okay to become yours alone
なんでもある日の
On a day where anything could happen
なんでもない キスしてね
Give me a casual kiss
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, 'I love you' isn't enough
君の特別にして
Make me your special one
ねえもっと Give me a kiss more 私は
Hey more, give me a kiss more, I am...
君でいっぱいよ
Full of thoughts of you
ほどけない リボン結び
A ribbon knot that won't come undone
小指ギュッて縛って
Tie our pinkies tight
そうよ一生 一生がいいの
Yes, forever, forever is best
特別チュが欲しい
I want a special kiss
二人きり 週末は
Just the two of us on the weekend
奏でてよ ハーモニー
Play our harmony
ネガイボシ 見たら
When you see a shooting star
私を思ってほしい
I want you to think of me
甘々な 君なのに
Even though you're so sweet
広い街 吸い込まれ
Sucked into the big city
戦う 姿に
Seeing you fighting
大きな 花丸だね
You get a big gold star
好きなとこ 優しいとこ
The things I like, your kindness
嫌いなとこも 優しいとこ
Even the things I hate, your kindness
誰にもあげない
I won't give you to anyone
私だけ 独り占め
Keeping you all to myself
うだって 今までの人と
Sweltering, and like people until now...
同じはいらないんです
I don't need things to be the same
ねえもっと Give me more love 私のため
Hey more, give me more love, for my sake
生きてほしいんです
I want you to live
だからうさぎと私は
That's why bunnies and I...
寂しくさせないで
Don't let us be lonely
そんなんじゃ 束縛じゃないわ
That's not enough to be called restraint
苦しいのが好き
I like it when it hurts
ショートケーキ 苺みたいに
Like the strawberry on a shortcake
座ってもいい？
Can I sit there?
赤く甘い 恋泥棒
A red, sweet love thief
誰か召し上がれ
Someone, please enjoy
大好きも 返してもらって
Get my 'love' back too
全部 私に
Give it all to me
頂戴 もっと
Give it to me, more
君は神様がつくる
You are made by God
奇跡のような人
A person like a miracle
つれた顔も その寝顔も
Your sulky face and your sleeping face
守ってあげるね
I'll protect them for you
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, 'I love you' isn't enough
君の特別にして
Make me your special one
ねえもっと Give me a kiss more 私は
Hey more, give me a kiss more, I am...
君でいっぱいよ
Full of thoughts of you
ほどけない リボン結び
A ribbon knot that won't come undone
小指ギュッて縛って
Tie our pinkies tight
ねえ Baby 最初で最後の
Hey baby, the first and last
特別にしてね
Make it special, okay?
うわあああ！
Uwaaaa!
天！天！天！天！天！天！
Heaven! Heaven! Heaven! Heaven! Heaven! Heaven!
天天天 天地創造 オープンセサミ
Ten-ten-ten, creation of heaven and earth, open sesame
闇と光の交わるアンフェリコ
The intersection of darkness and light, Inferico
今宵味わうサイケデリック
Tonight, we taste the psychedelic
踊り絡まり合うゾディアック
Dancing and intertwining Zodiac
恋の駆け引きのタイブレイク
The tie-break of love's tactics
飾らない存在 ただ気を惹きたい
An unadorned existence, I just want to attract your attention
夢見心地 触れ合い 惑わせたい
A dreamy feeling, touching, I want to lead you astray
曖昧 解けない ここで...
Ambiguity, cannot be solved, here...
甘い
Sweet...
鮮やかな赤い愛
Vivid red love
見つめて限界
Looking until the limit
月夜に誘われて
Lured by the moonlit night
天使と悪魔と
Angel and devil
悪魔が甘さ過失した
The devil made a sweet mistake
天国
Heaven
地獄の
Hell's
天国
Heaven
地獄の
Hell's
天国
Heaven
地獄の狭間で出会った
Met in the threshold of Hell
天使と悪魔と
Angel and devil
悪魔が集って踊れば
When devils gather and dance
天国
Heaven
地獄の
Hell's
天国 地獄の門が開く
The gates of Heaven and Hell open
闇と光の交わるファナティック
Fanatic where darkness and light intersect
今宵味わうサイケデリック
Tonight, savor the psychedelic
踊り絡み合うゾディアック
Zodiac dancing and intertwining
恋の駆け引きのダイブブレイク
A dive break in the game of love
Dead or Alive
Desu desu desu
Death death death
Bass bass bass
生きた魂をトレイに置いて
Place the living soul on a tray
巡る五枚のカード 揺れる炎
Five rotating cards, flickering flames
先にあなたがリリースしたら
If you release first...
もう迷わない グラス飲み干して
No more hesitation, drain the glass
今夜オールイン 降りないこの勝負
Tonight, all-in, won't back down from this match
今 天国と地獄を繋ぐ門が開く
Now, the gate connecting Heaven and Hell opens
天使と悪魔 死者と生者が入り乱れ
Angels and devils, the dead and living jumbled
踊り 笑い 全ては混沌の中に飲み込まれて行く
Dancing, laughing, everything swallowed by chaos
それは世界の終焉であり 新たなる始まりでもあるのだった
It was the end of the world, and a new beginning
Ten Ten Ten Ten 天国 Ten
Ten ten ten ten Heaven ten
Ten Ten Ten Ten 天国 地獄
Ten ten ten ten Heaven and Hell
月夜に誘われて
Lured by the moonlit night
天使と悪魔と
Angel and devil
悪魔が甘さ過失した
The devil made a sweet mistake
天国
Heaven
地獄の
Hell's
恍惚消えない 果てない 胸ない
Ecstasy doesn't fade, endless, breathless
天国 地獄の... 狭間で出会った
Heaven and Hell's... Met in the threshold
天使と悪魔と... 悪魔が集って踊れば
Angel and devil... When devils gather and dance
Dance Dance Dance
Iblis dari mana?
Where is this devil from?
Wah gataunya orang iblis...
Wow, I didn't know you were a devil...
Wahai!
Oh my!
Itu, empat tanduk bahaya sekali.
Those four horns are very dangerous.
Iya jadi gini... Aku datang jauh-jauh...
So, it's like this... I came from afar...
Meskipun tidak diundang!
Even though I wasn't invited!
Oh diundang!
Oh, I was invited!
Iya kayaknya kamu ngundang yang lain deh tadi.
Yeah, I think you invited someone else earlier.
Maksudnya? Do you mean?
What do you mean? Do you mean?
Kenapa tiba-tiba Nihongo?
Why suddenly Japanese?
Kamu malaikat Jepang ya?
Are you a Japanese angel?
Bisa berhenti muter nggak? Pusing.
Can you stop spinning? It's dizzying.
Malaikat kok pusing guys?
An angel is dizzy, guys?
Iya aku di sini soalnya datang buat ngerayu kamu aja sebenarnya.
Yeah, I'm here because I actually just came to seduce you.
Pengen main bareng, pengen godain kamu aja.
Want to play together, just want to tease you.
Sini sini sini...
Come here, come here...
Pulang kamu habis ini.
You're going home after this.
Loh? Kamu habis ini pulang sama aku kan?
Eh? You're going home with me after this, right?
Pulang?
Going home?
Habis ini nggak ada apa-apa lagi kan? Ngapain enak-enak aku di atas...
Nothing else after this, right? Why am I comfortable up here...
Masa kamu seret aku?
You want to drag me?
Loh kita... loh bukannya kita...
Eh we... eh weren't we...
Kita... kita... lu aja iblis!
We... we... you're just a devil!
Ajak dong, ajak dong bang!
Invite me, invite me bro!
Kamu saya ajak!
I invite you!
Aku kesepian... Ayo sini bareng...
I'm lonely... Come here together...
Fallen angel nih!
Fallen angel here!
Gak gak gak ada fallen angel!
No no no, there's no fallen angel!
Waktunya aku panah! Panah asmara!
It's time I shoot my arrow! Arrow of love!
1 2 3... ぷっ！
1 2 3... Puh!
How to tame your demon.
Jadi light novel.
It becomes a light novel.
Eh tapi tadi keren banget lho guys.
But that was really cool earlier, guys.
Iya lucu gak.
Yeah, wasn't it cute?
Atas!
Up!
Bawah!
Down!
Atas!
Up!
Bawah!
Down!
Atas!
Up!
Terus tadi pas kamu atas, aku bawah.
Then earlier when you were up, I was down.
Kebalik.
Reversed.
Tau ya, orang mah kebalik kiri kanan.
I know, right? Usually people reverse left and right.
Dia aku bilang tetap atas.
She... I told her to stay up.
Atas!
Up!
Aku bawah.
I'm down.
Atas!
Up!
Kocak, kocak.
Funny, funny.
Ya udah.
Alright then.
Ya udah kalau gitu, aku...
Alright then, I...
Aku wanita sibuk ya sebenernya.
I'm actually a busy woman.
Jadi kayak emang nggak ada gitu banyak waktu.
So like, there really isn't much time.
Aku di sini mampir.
I'm just stopping by here.
Mampir dikit aja bentaran.
Just stopping by for a little bit.
Kasih tiga, kasih lima detik buat kamu.
Giving three, giving five seconds for you.
Buset, pemimpin neraka nih.
Damn, a leader of hell right here.
Asik.
Cool.
Oke.
Okay.
Baik.
Good.
Fiksi ya guys, ini cerita fiksi, jangan ditiru adik-adik.
It's fiction, guys. This is a fictional story, don't imitate it, kids.
Fiksi, fiksi.
Fiction, fiction.
Sensitif ini, sensitif.
This is sensitive, sensitive.
Fiksi, boongan.
Fiction, fake.
Oke kalau gitu, bye!
Okay then, bye!
Nggak mau ikut aku?
Don't want to come with me?
Bye bye bye bye!
Jagain nih anak ya guys.
Watch over this kid, guys.
Kita lihat perilakunya beneran seiso atau nggak.
Let's see if her behavior is really seiso or not.
Lihat tuh, lihat tuh gayanya. Jagain, jagain.
Look at that, look at her style. Watch her, watch her.
Ya udah, bye!
Alright, bye!
Bisa jadi fallen angel aku karena hasutan dia, guys.
I might become a fallen angel because of her provocation, guys.
Nggak jelas.
Makes no sense.
どきどきキュン!で大暴走♡
Dokidoki Kyun! Going Wild♡
何とかしなくちゃならなくて
I had to do something
突然メイドになっちゃって
And suddenly I became a maid
いつものように お店の掃除
Cleaning the shop as usual
扉 開いちゃって目が合った
The door opened and our eyes met
何だか じゅわ〜ん しちゃいそうで
I felt like I was about to sizzle
突然メイドになっちゃって
Suddenly I became a maid
あわてんぼうにもなっちゃって
I even became a scatterbrain
お仕事中にも 推しに夢中に
Even while working, I'm crazy for my 'oshi'
どこを探しても見当たらないじゃん
I can't find them anywhere no matter where I look
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もういいよ
That's enough
秘密だよね
It's a secret, right?
もういいの
It's okay
好きになっちゃって
I've fallen in love
ねぇ
Hey
好きって言って
Say you love me
どきどきキュン！ 送るラブビーム
Doki doki kyun! Sending a love beam
君も夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's magic that makes you crazy too, isn't it?
ほら どきどきキュン！
Look, doki doki kyun!
私 大暴走
I'm going out of control
君を夢中にさせる 恋の味
The taste of love that makes you crazy
もう君にキュン！ 私大暴走
Already kyun for you! I'm out of control
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic where we can be crazy together
だから君がキュンってなる恋になって
So let this be a love that makes you go 'kyun'
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
Have one, please; this is the taste of love
楽しくて仕方なくたって
Even though it's so much fun I can't help it
そろそろ終わりになっちゃって
It's almost time for it to end
会いたくなって 落ち込んじゃって
I want to see you, and I feel down
君とぶつかって 目が合った
I bumped into you and our eyes met
何度も会いたくなっちゃって
I keep wanting to see you more and more
今日だけじゃ足りないんだって
Today alone isn't enough
計画通り 私の勝利
Just as planned, it's my victory
君に会いたくて仕方が無いよ
I can't help wanting to see you
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もういいの
It's okay
君だけだよ
It's only you
もうずっと
Forever
愛し合いたいよ
I want to love you
ねぇ
Hey
好きって言って
Say you love me
どきどきキュン！ 君にラブビーム
Doki doki kyun! Love beam to you
二人夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic where both of us can be crazy
ほら どきどきキュン！ 私大恋愛
Look, doki doki kyun! I'm deeply in love
君も夢中にさせる恋のまき
Makes you crazy too, the 'love chapter'
も〜！ 君にキュン！ 私大好物
Geez! Kyun for you! You're my favorite thing
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic where I can be crazy with you
だから君はキュンってなる恋におちて
So fall in a love that makes you go 'kyun'
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
Have one, please; this is the taste of love
もしも このままだったら
If it stayed like this
ここで会うこともなくなって
And we stopped meeting here
もう 君の声が
Already, your voice...
聞きたくなるの
I'll start wanting to hear it
もう一回
One more time
ちょっと待って
Wait a minute
もういいの
It's okay
秘密なのに
Even though it's a secret
もういいよ
That's enough
このまま好きになっていく
I'm going to keep falling in love with you
ねぇ
Hey
好きって言って
Say you love me
どきどきキュン！ 送るラブビーム
Doki doki kyun! Sending a love beam
君を夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's magic that makes you crazy, isn't it?
ほら どきどきキュン！ 私大暴走
Look, doki doki kyun! I'm going out of control
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
The taste of love that makes you crazy
も〜！ 君にキュン！ 私大暴走
Geez! Kyun for you! I'm out of control
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic where I can be crazy with you
だから君がキュンってなる恋になって
So let this be a love that makes you go 'kyun'
ひとつどうぞこれが恋の味
Have one, please; this is the taste of love
Halo semuanya!
Hello everyone!
Hehe, langit udah mulai gelap tapi...
Hehe, the sky has started to get dark but...
Masih pada semangat nggak semuanya?!
Are you all still energetic?!
アーニャとパフォーマンスしてから
After performing with Anya,
次は こぼはまた一人で歌いたいなと思います
next, Kobo wants to sing alone once more.
これから歌うこの曲は 最近こぼが気に入っている曲で
This next song I'm going to sing is one that I've really liked lately,
聴いたら幸せな気持ちになりました
and it made me feel happy when I heard it.
皆さんもこの曲聴いて 幸せを感じてくれたら嬉しいです
I hope you all can listen to this song and feel that happiness too.
それでは 次の曲
Now then, the next song.
青野てるまさんの「Happiness」です
By Aono Teruma, 'Happiness.'
君と Happiness どんな時も
You and Happiness, no matter when,
ひとりじゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that I'm not alone.
何も言わなくても 感じてるよ The One for Me
Even if you don't say anything, I can feel it, you're the one for me.
「Happiness」 作詞: 青野てるま・H.U.B. / 作曲: 豊田裕喜
'Happiness' Lyrics: Aono Teruma, H.U.B. / Music: Yuki Toyoda
You always make me happy...
打ち込んで 眠れなくて
Caught up in things, unable to sleep,
君との写真 見つめている
I'm staring at photos of us.
いくつもの笑顔たちに
By those many smiles,
助けられるよ My Life
my life is saved.
ずっと一緒だよ 泣いてもいいよ
We'll always be together, it's okay to cry.
あの涙を抱きしめてくれた
You embraced those tears.
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
ここにいるから
I'm right here,
すぐに会いたいよ
I want to see you right away.
君と Happiness 君がいれば
You and Happiness, if you are here,
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be okay.
何も言わなくても
Even if you don't say anything,
感じてるよ The One for Me
I can feel it, you're the one for me.
君と Happiness どんな時も
You and Happiness, no matter when,
ひとりじゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that I'm not alone.
涙溢れたって
Even if tears overflow,
歩けるよ Please stay by my side
I can walk on, please stay by my side.
君に出会えてからは
Since I met you,
素直に笑っていられるよ
I've been able to smile honestly.
少しずつ自分のこと
Little by little, myself...
好きになれた For Your Love
I've come to like, for your love.
そう今なら ねぇ心から
Yes, now, from the bottom of my heart,
わかりあえるって思えるよ
I feel like we can understand each other.
強がらずにありのままで
Without acting tough, just as I am,
見つめてくれた
you looked at me.
だから Happiness 君の事を
So Happiness, about you,
今よりもっと知りたくて
I want to know even more than now.
どんな言葉よりも
More than any words,
大切な The One for Me
precious, you're the one for me.
私も君に何か
I also want to do
できることしたいよ
something for you.
いつでも一緒だから
Because we're always together,
守っていけるから
I can protect you,
ずっと
forever.
君と Happiness 君がいれば
You and Happiness, if you are here,
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be okay.
何も言わなくても
Even if you don't say anything,
感じてるよ The One for Me
I can feel it, you're the one for me.
君と Happiness どんな時も
You and Happiness, no matter when,
ひとりじゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that I'm not alone.
涙溢れたって
Even if tears overflow,
歩けるよ Please stay by my side
I can walk on, please stay by my side.
大切な The One for Me
Precious, the one for me.
Yeah! Let's go!
You always make me happy...
Oh oh oh...
Smile for me baby...
You always make me happy...
モエチャッカファイア
Moechakkafire
ようこそお越しなさったご主人様
Welcome, my dear master
隣に座って せーの
Come sit beside me and say now...
もえ もえ もえ もえ
Moe moe, moe moe
こんなんで誰が喜ぶの？
Who would be happy with this?
さあね教えて 笑顔でアップアップ
I don't know, tell me. With a smile, up, up
理想は逸れて ご苦労様
The ideal is straying, thanks for your hard work
私とあなたで せーの
You and me together, say now...
ララララ
La la la la
こんなんで誰が喜ぶの？
Who would be happy with this?
さあね教えて 笑顔でアップアップ
I don't know, tell me. With a smile, up, up
フラリフラリ女の子
Wandering, wandering girl
ふわふわ言葉の層
Fluffy, fluffy layers of words
それらすべてつまり収めな
In short, take them all in
感情的にある 笑顔でアップアップ
It's emotional. With a smile, up, up
人は見かけによらぬもの
People are not what they seem
嘘を嘘だと見抜けない
Can't see through a lie as a lie
したたかそうで おそるおかわ
Seemingly cunning, yet fearful
あ、鳥肌 寒気 あんどトワイライト
Ah, goosebumps, chills, and the twilight
間違ったご主人様を頂きます
I'll take the wrong master
私とあなたで せーの
You and me together, say now...
ララララ
La la la la
これはど派手に ご苦労様
This is flashy, thanks for your hard work
遊びましょう 笑顔でアップアップ
Let's play. With a smile, up, up
フラリフラリ ここはどこ？
Wandering, wandering, where am I?
ふわふわ 外はミッション
Fluffy, fluffy, outside is a mission
それらすべてつまり収めな
In short, take them all in
感情的にある 笑顔でアップアップ
It's emotional. With a smile, up, up
歌い出す 秘密の鐘
Secret bells start to sing
終わることのない この世界
In this world that never ends
悲しい子供は 悲しい子供は
Sad children, sad children...
眠らせて 眠らせて
...let them sleep, let them sleep
孫娘ごと 遊びましょう
Let's play with the granddaughter too
笑顔でアップアップ
With a smile, up, up
フラリフラリ女の子
Wandering, wandering girl
ふわふわ言葉の層
Fluffy, fluffy layers of words
それらすべて つまり収めな
In short, take them all in
感情的にある 笑顔でアップアップ
It's emotional. With a smile, up, up
あ、鳥肌 寒気 あんどトワイライト
Ah, goosebumps, chills, and the twilight
間違ったご主人様を頂きます
I'll take the wrong master
私とあなたで せーの
You and me together, say now...
ララララ
La la la la
あ、鳥肌 寒気 あんどトワイライト
Ah, goosebumps, chills, and the twilight
間違ったご主人様を頂きます
I'll take the wrong master
私とあなたで せーの
You and me together, say now...
ララララ ララララ
La la la la, la la la la
SUNDAY NIGHT MAGIC
Let's dance with me
Ooh...
何回でもかける TRUE MAGIC
I'll cast true magic as many times as I want
まだまだ今日は夢心地
Today still feels like a dream
Yo 眠たくても簡単再現
Yo, even if I'm sleepy, it's easy reproduction
何度でもおかえりって once again
Welcome back, once again
朝が来るその時まで
Until the time the morning comes
ねえ 僕とどうだい
Hey, how about with me?
塞ぎ込んでる週の終わりに
At the end of a gloomy week
退屈そうだけど どうだろう
You look bored, but how about it?
誘っていいかな
Is it okay to invite you?
Come on night, Come on night, 構わない
Come on night, come on night, I don't care
どっち向いてる？ こっち向いてる？
Which way are you looking? Looking this way?
あっち向いては なんかじゃなくて
It's not about looking that way
君のことだもん
It's about you
もっとちゃんと話聞かせてよ
Let me hear you talk more properly
Hey Let's see からが逆転
Hey, it's a turnaround from "Let's see"
昨日より今日の方が 可愛いし
Today is even cuter than yesterday
いても立ってもいられない
I can't just sit still
聞こえる ゼロの告げるチャイム
I can hear the chime at zero
時間切れも駆け足で
Running even when time is up
飛び出して かけ出して
Jumping out, running out
まだまだ夜終われない
The night isn't over yet
こんな最高な日々が
Such a wonderful day
明日も続いてくんなら
If it continues tomorrow too
ねえ 君もどうだい
Hey, how about you too?
待ち望んでる君の理想の
Waiting for your ideal...
お姫様の席を
...princess seat
どうしよう 狙っていいかな
What should I do? Is it okay to aim for it?
ねきちゃん すてきちゃん
Neki-chan, Suteki-chan
えい いまじゃない
Ei, not right now
ねこも尺しーも 僕に合わせ
Even cats and everything, match me
で ステップなんか踏んでみて
And try taking some steps
ご機嫌そう
Looking like you're in a good mood
昨日より今日の方が ずっと楽しくて
Today is much more fun than yesterday
続けていたい時には
When I want to keep going
聞こえる ゼロの告げるチャイム
I can hear the chime at zero
時間切れも駆け足で
Running even when time is up
終わらない 止まらない
Won't end, won't stop
まだまだ夜長いから
Because the night is still long
こんな最高な日々が
Such a wonderful day
音に乗って
Riding on the sound
身体を預けてみたら
If you try to surrender your body
ほら 魔法みたい
Look, it's like magic
Time in the club
Could be swallow
騒がしくて馬鹿らしいようなプライド 毎日がいい
A noisy and silly pride, every day is good
魔法なんてありえない
Magic isn't possible
でも今夜だけは現実になるかも
But maybe tonight it will become real
Are you love step?
音に登って驚き君も
Climbing the sound, you'll be surprised too
終わらない夜に とびっきりの魔法
In the endless night, a special magic
君にもかけてあげるから
Because I'll cast it on you too
僕の手をとってよ
Take my hand
うわあ！
Whoa!
ここはどこ！？
Where are we!?
わかんにゃい！
I don't know!
え、なんか雲美味しそうじゃない？
Hey, don't those clouds look delicious?
食べてみなよ！
Try eating some!
おいちー！
Tasty!
おいしい！
Delicious!
何がしてるの！？
What are you doing!?
あ、こぼちゃーん！
Ah, Kobo-chan!
はじめは食べてないです！
I wasn't eating them at first!
Kobo, calm down! Today is your birthday!
あ、誕生日！
Ah, my birthday!
Happy Birthday!
あ、ありがとう！
Ah, thank you!
こぼ先輩と一緒に歌って踊りたい！
I want to sing and dance with Kobo-senpai!
歌って踊りたい！
Want to sing and dance!
Koboの振り付け！
Kobo's choreography!
こぼ先生と呼んでください！
Please call me Kobo-sensei!
勉強した？
Did you study?
もちろん！
Of course!
誰も居なくなった
There's nobody left
二人だけの街に
In this town of only two of us
機械仕掛けの時計が
A mechanical clock
夜の訪れ知らせる
Announces the arrival of the night
夕闇が空を
Twilight dyes the sky
ワイン色に染めて
In the color of wine
不慣れな二人
We, two inexperienced
舞台へと誘う
Are invited to the stage
Just away, I'm notch or two
あなたに魔法をあげる
I'll cast a spell on you
To away, I'm a password
その名前はハニー
That name is Honey
蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Mitsuketsu An-Deux-Trois
互いの指を絡めて
Entwining our fingers
Singing, swinging, swinging sweet a song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing our dream
Chase and whisk and natural tour
あなたに魔法をかけて
I'll cast a spell on you
Throw away and over sway
魅惑の蜜を編んでいく
Weaving this enchanting nectar
蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un, Deux, Trois
あの唇を重ねて
Our lips touch once again
Singing, swinging, swinging sweet a song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing our love
月明かりが街を
The moonlight bathes the town
黄金色に照らして
Shining in a golden hue
幼い二人は
As two inexperienced souls
つまずきながら踊る
Dance and stumble along
蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un, Deux, Trois
互いの指を絡めて
Our fingers entwined together
Singing, swinging, swinging sweet a song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing our dream
Sha-ba-da-ba 蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Sha-ba-da-ba Honeymoon Un, Deux, Trois
その唇を重ねて
Our lips touch once again
Singing, swinging, swinging sweet a song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing our love
楽しかったー！
That was so much fun!
やったー！
We did it!
ダンス上手！ダンス上手！
Great dancing! Great dancing!
Terima kasih, Kobo-chan.
Thank you, Kobo-chan.
Kobo先輩もスワン...
Kobo-senpai was like a swan...
スワン！スワン！
Swan! Swan!
Beautiful スワン...
A beautiful swan...
めっちゃエレガント！
So elegant!
あ、難しかった！
Ah, that was hard!
楽しかったー
It was fun.
見てくれてありがとね
Thanks for watching.
Kobo先輩 呼んでくれてありがちょ！
Kobo-senpai, thanks for inviting me!
一緒に踊ってくれてもありがとう。
Thanks for dancing with me too.
Terima kasih!
Thank you!
Sama-sama! Sama-sama!
You're welcome! You're welcome!
Happy Birthday!
おめでとー！
Congrats!
じゃあ、バイバイ！
Alright, bye-bye!
みんな帰っちゃった。
Everyone's gone home.
寂しい... 悲しい...
I'm lonely... I'm sad...
誰も来ないのかな。
I wonder if no one else is coming.
さよならの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye
さよならの後は 忘れさせて
Let me forget after we say goodbye
でも あなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away
離れない 話せない 戻りたい
Can't leave, can't speak, I want to go back
Take me free
この歌は君へ歌った歌
This song is the one I sang for you
二人だけの秘密
A secret just for the two of us...
部屋の中は香水だらけに染めた
The room was stained with perfume...
Jasmine Flavor
当たり前さえも奇跡
Even the ordinary is a miracle,
当たり触れない君との軌跡
a trajectory with you, untouched.
どれだけ恋知っても
No matter how much I know about love,
超えられない君を
I still can't get over you.
今ならわかる気がして
I feel like I understand now...
今から過去にも戻れるなら
If I could return to the past now...
さよならの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye.
さよならの後は 忘れさせて
After the goodbye, let me forget.
でも あなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I won't leave you.
話せない
I can't let go.
戻りたい
I want to go back.
Take me free...
呪いたいほど愛しているのよ
I love you so much it hurts,
気付けば あなたのことばかり浮かべて
before I knew it, I was only thinking of you.
明日になれば大丈夫
It'll be okay by tomorrow...
何度も言い聞かせればいいの
just how many times should I tell myself that?
愛という沼に 溺れてる
I'm drowning in a swamp called love.
私の声は 届かない
My voice doesn't reach you.
さよならの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye.
さよならの後は 忘れさせて
After the goodbye, let me forget.
でも あなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I won't leave you.
話せない
I can't let go.
戻りたい
I want to go back.
Take me...
さよならの前に キスをして
Kiss me before we say goodbye.
さよならの後は 忘れさせて
After the goodbye, let me forget.
でも あなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't fade away.
離れない
I won't leave you.
話さない
I won't let go.
戻りたい
I want to go back.
Take me free...
変えない日々 抱きしめたまま
While holding onto those unchanging days...
いつか そう いつか
Someday, yes, someday...
弱い心が 捕まる前に
Before my weak heart gets caught...
そっと あなたを遠ざけた
I quietly pushed you away.
あー こんな気持ち つらすぎるよ もう
Ah, these feelings are too painful now.
あなたは 誰なの どこに隠れてたの
Who are you? Where were you hiding?
ひどく 怯えてる うつむいたままの
Terribly frightened, with my head bowed...
見えぬなら 私が願ってた
If I can't see, then I was wishing...
またあの季節 夜空は白く
That season again, the night sky turns white.
あなたもいて
You were there too.
触れてこないで 嬉しいけど
Don't touch me, although I'm happy...
心が痛い
My heart hurts.
離したくない 離れたくない
I don't want to let go, I don't want to leave.
でも 諦めてた
But I had given up.
もうこれ以上 好きになれない
I can't love you any more than this.
失う痛み 耐えきれないよ
I can't bear the pain of losing you.
変えない日々 抱きしめたまま
While holding onto those unchanging days...
いつか そう いつか
Someday, yes, someday...
ただそばにいて それだけでいい
Just stay by my side, that's all I need.
素直には なれないけれど
Although I can't be honest...
さあ 声を上げて 歩み始めなきゃ
Come on, raise your voice and start walking
Realize 私よ 気づいて
Realize, it's me, notice me
また あの季節 この空の下 見上げている
Again, that season, beneath this sky, I'm looking up
傷ついたもの もう 元には 戻らないけれど
Things that were hurt won't ever return to the way they were, but...
あー 離したくない 離れたくない
Ah, I don't want to let go, I don't want to be apart
もう 諦めない
I won't give up anymore
あなたの心 傷つけてでも
Even if I hurt your heart
この気持ちに 嘘はつけない
I can't lie to these feelings
いつか 笑顔で 話せるような
So that one day we can talk with a smile
私を 見つけて
Find the me that...
あー そばにいて 聞かせてほしい
Ah, stay by my side, I want you to tell me
二度と 一人には しないと
That you'll never leave me alone again
返らない日々 抱きしめたまま
While embracing the days that won't return
きっと そう きっと
Surely, yes, surely
あの日の気持ち 受け止めないと
I have to accept the feelings of that day
前に 進むことができない
Or I won't be able to move forward
離したくない 離れたくない
Don't want to let go, don't want to be apart
一つの願いは
My one wish is...
大好きだよと 伝えたいだけ
I just want to tell you that I love you
本当 素直じゃないけれど
Even though I'm not really honest
So, how is it guys?
That was "Closing".
Did you take a lot of screenshots?
And how about my new stage?
Look!
It's very cloudy here.
There's two big Chill-Lous on the left and right.
So cute, right?
みんなどうだった？コボのパフォーマンス。
How was it, everyone? Kobo's performance.
いっぱいスクリーンショット撮れたかな？うん。
Did you get lots of screenshots? Yeah.
コボの新しいステージはもうどうだった？
What did you think of Kobo's new stage?
可愛いでしょ？
It's cute, right?
ビグチルスがありますのでめちゃ可愛いよね。
The Big Chill-Lous are here, so it's super cute, right?
So actually, yeah, we're already at the end of the show guys.
そろそろお別れの時間になります。
It's almost time to say goodbye.
But don't worry.
Kobo still has something to share with you guys.
まだ皆さんにお知らせがあります。
I still have an announcement for everyone.
ジャン ジャジャーン！
Ta-da!
Kobo Kanaeru Birthday 2025 Merchandise
Princess...
I've wanted to wear a jellyfish costume
for a long time.
And finally, my wish came true.
So, how is it, guys?
Do I look beautiful? Ni-ni-ni-ni.
Do I look beautiful? Hehe.
And the KV is drawn by Scottie sensei.
スコッティ先生、ありがとう！
Scottie sensei, thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
And as you wish, guys...
Finally, tada!
Kobokers' Happi is here!
Now you guys can be proud Kobokers and perfect
for cheering me during events.
Keren banget. Happi, Happi, Happi.
It's so cool. Happi, Happi, Happi.
Come on buy Happi, Happi, Happi.
And if you look closely, this Happi design is like
my raincoat, right?
And you can see there's chills in the front and me
in the back. Right?
And next!
We have this "Jellyfish Princess on the Wall"
Tapestry.
It's printed with my brand new birthday
illustration.
It's super high quality and perfect for
decorating your wall.
You can wake up and see Kobo's smug face
every morning.
And also don't forget to praise the Lord
every day.
Then, look at this!
The "Jellyfish Princess, you got this"
Button Badge Set. Two pieces.
One has my birthday outfit and the other is an
illustration I drew by myself.
Yeah, by myself. It looks good, right?
Do you like it? I drew it by myself.
So you can pin them to your bag, or your hat,
or your heart.
This one is one of my favorites.
One, two, three... tada!
The Plushie Keychain!
It's me, but mini Kobo in mini form.
You can bring me anywhere on your backpack,
your keys...
...your motorcycle, the car, or whatever, even
next to your computer while you watch my streams.
So soft and squishy.
And finally...
We also have the Situational Voice Pack.
So it's called "Your One and Only Jellyfish
Princess". What does it mean?
Buy it, buy it okay, so you know what does it mean.
It's a special voice pack where I talk to you
about Jellyfish Princess...
...and you know, your one and only just for you.
Yeah, don't miss out my birthday merch guys.
If you buy a set of them, you'll get a special
bromide with my signature on it.
The merch is available for a limited time only,
so you can grab yours...
...from the official shop.
Links are in the description.
So yeah, that's all for the announcement.
Thank you for coming and watching Kobo
performance today.
以上グッズとお知らせでした。
That's all for the merchandise and announcements.
説明欄やチャット欄にリンクを貼ってありますので、
Links are in the description and chat section,
クリックしてね。おーよ！
so please click them. Oh yeah!
But I can hear some of you want an encore, hmm?
アンコール、アンコールほしい？
Encore, encore, you want an encore?
じゃ、しょうがないわ…
Well, I guess I have no choice...
Sweet Memories
あ〜
Ah~
Sweet Memories
なつかしい痛みだわ
This pain is nostalgic
ずっと前に忘れていた
I forgot it a long time ago, but...
でもあなたを見たとき
When I saw you,
時間だけが後戻りしたの
only time went back.
「幸福？」と聞かないで
Don't ask, “Are you happy?”
嘘つくのは上手じゃない
I'm not good at telling a lie
友だちならいるけど
I have some friends, but...
あんなには燃えあがれなくて
I'm now unable to become passionate like before
失った夢だけが
Why do only lost dreams look...
美しく見えるのはなぜかしら
so beautiful?
過ぎ去ったやさしさも今は
The kindness that has passed is now...
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
Sweet memories, Sweet memories
キスしたらいけないわ
If we kissed, it wouldn't be right...
傷をひとつ増やすだけよ
We'd only be adding one more scar
長いあいだあなたに
For a long time...
会いたくて泣いていたくせに
although I'd been crying because I wanted to see you
あの頃は若すぎて
Back then, we were too young...
いたずらに傷つけあった二人
and the two of us hurt each other for no reason
色あせた悲しみも今は
Even the faded sadness is now...
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
Sweet memories, Sweet memories
失った
Only lost...
夢だけが
dreams...
美しく見えるのはなぜかしら
why do they look so beautiful?
過ぎ去ったやさしさも今は
The kindness that has passed is now...
甘い記憶 Sweet memories
Sweet memories, Sweet memories
フィナーレ
Finale
君はほんとにわかってないよ
You really don't understand it
例えばハッピーエンドより
For example, rather than a happy ending
甘くて豪華なデザートより
Rather than a sweet and luxurious dessert
君がいいんだよ
I want you
ふたつの傘より相合い傘
Sharing an umbrella, rather than two umbrellas
ちょっと冷たいけど
It's a little cold, but
「愛するための」代償なら いくらでもどうぞ
If it's the price for 'loving,' take however much
ただずっと側にいたい
I just want to be by your side forever
ねえダーリン
Hey, darling
Oh 星屑もない二人ぼっちの世界で
Oh, in a world of just us two, with no stardust
ずっと最後の花火をあげて
Always, set off the last fireworks
フィナーレを飾って
Decorate the finale
奇跡の降る
In a world where miracles fall
ねえダーリン
Hey, darling
Oh いつか今日を忘れても
Oh, even if one day you forget today
君がいるんだよ
I'm here, I'm here
味気ない世界も悪くないね
Even a dull world isn't so bad
どんなに恋をしたって
No matter how many times I fall in love
出会えないよきっと
I'm sure I'll never find anyone like you
終わりもない 幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss our endless happiness
いつか今日を忘れても
Even if one day you forget today
君がいるんだよ
I'm here, I'm here
電気雨の降る夜も
Even on the night when the electric rain falls
愛し合った日から
Starting from the day we loved each other
目が合った日から
And the day our eyes met
ずっと覚えてるよ
I'll always remember that
ねえダーリン
Hey, darling
Oh 星屑もない二人ぼっちの世界で
Oh, in a world of just us two, with no stardust
ずっと最後の花火をあげて
Always, set off the last fireworks
フィナーレを誓って
Pledge the finale
奇跡の降る
In a world where miracles fall
ねえダーリン
Hey, darling
Oh いつか今日を忘れても
Oh, even if one day you forget today
離さないで
Don't let me go
呆気ない世界も悪くないね
Even a sudden world isn't so bad
どんなに恋をしたって
No matter how many times I fall in love
忘れられないのきっと
I'm sure I can't forget you
終わりもない 幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss our endless happiness
味気ないね
It's tasteless, isn't it?
でもそれかね
But maybe that's why
二人の幸せ
Our happiness
Oh my god, I almost cried.
I almost cried singing this song.
Thank you for today, guys!
Thank you for today.
Thank you for watching until the end.
And thank you for Zeta-chi,
because she covered this finale
song first,
and then I was inspired, so yeah...
Aku baru lagunya di sini, hehe.
I just learned the song here, hehe.
今日は来てくれて、
Thank you for coming today,
最後まで見てくれてありがとうございます！
and watching until the end!
I hope you guys enjoyed all the
performances,
um, yeah, this whole stream.
みんな大好き！
Thank you for your birthday wishes.
I love you all!
あとで読んであげますね。
I'll read them later.
バイバイ、みんな。
No more encore, no more encore.
Bye-bye, everyone.
バイバイ。
Bye-bye.
Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day.
Bye-bye!